<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel> 
	<atom:link href="http://pendantbooks.com/blog/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<title>James Batchelor Blog</title>
	<link>http://www.pendantbooks.com/blog/</link>
	<description>Blog</description>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<image>
		<title>Pendant Books</title>
		<link>http://www.pendantbooks.com/blog/</link>
		<url>http://www.pendantbooks.com/images/pendant_clear.png</url>
		<width>144</width>
		<height>124</height>
	</image>
	<item>
		<title>Keeping My Promise</title>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 14:33:00 MST</pubDate>
		<link>http://www.pendantbooks.com/2022/08/19/keeping-my-promise.html</link>
		<description><![CDATA[As promised in my previous post from less than seven months ago, I have an update on the projects currently underway.]]></description>	
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>What I Learned from a Spammer</title>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 14:33:00 MST</pubDate>
		<link>http://www.pendantbooks.com/2022/07/19/what-I-learned-from-a-spammer.html</link>
		<description><![CDATA[I don’t get much spam email these days. With the increased efficiency of spam filters, and the fact that I serve up a spam email address to pretty much any system that asks for an email, not too much gets through. But I do get one. Every Tuesday, like clockwork, I receive an unsolicited email from a woman pushing health supplements. I do not know how she got my info, but here’s the weird part: when I go to delete her emails, I invariably find myself reading them. Why? Because they are short. She usually has about a paragraph of text that she divides up into discrete lines, like a bulleted list. Without even meaning to, I find myself scanning the text and often being drawn in.]]></description>	
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Answers to Commonly Asked Questions</title>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 14:33:00 MST</pubDate>
		<link>http://www.pendantbooks.com/2021/11/29/answers-to-common-questions.html</link>
		<description><![CDATA[When people learn that I am a writer a number of questions usually follow. “What kind of books do you write?” is usually the first. But when they grow more comfortable, questions about my books specifically usually turn to questions about writing or publishing in general]]></description>	
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Red Flags for Big Publishing Houses</title>
		<pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2014 14:33:00 MST</pubDate>
		<link>http://www.pendantbooks.com/2014/11/28/red-flags-for-big-publishing-houses.html</link>
		<description><![CDATA[The world of Publishing has changed dramatically over the last decade. There is no doubt about it. We live in a time when anyone, regardless of subject matter or talent, can publish their work to the world with the investment of nothing more than time. And though there are often many reasons]]></description>
		
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Recapturing the Magic</title>
		<pubDate>Sun, 3 Aug 2014 14:33:00 MDT</pubDate>
		<link>http://www.pendantbooks.com/2014/08/03/recapturing-the-magic.html</link>
		<description><![CDATA[As I announced some months ago via twitter and facebook, I have finished the rough draft of Hall of Mages. Now some of you are starting to notice that you have not heard any updates since then.]]></description>
		
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>My Writing Process</title>
		<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2014 14:33:00 MDT</pubDate>
		<link>http://www.pendantbooks.com/2014/06/22/my-writing-process.html</link>
		<description><![CDATA[I am posting today as a participant in an author’s blog-hop, wherein a bunch of different authors answer four of the most commonly asked questions that we authors hear.]]></description>
		
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>It Was Never About Talent</title>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2013 14:33:00 MDT</pubDate>
		<link>http://www.pendantbooks.com/2013/06/13/it-was-never-about-talent.html</link>
		<description><![CDATA[Do you ever worry that you are not talented enough to make a go of it in a creative field? Do you watch these hacks on the televised talent shows who are reduced to tears when they are rejected and fear that maybe that is you?]]></description>
		
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Just Do The Work</title>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 March 2013 14:33:00 MDT</pubDate>
		<link>http://www.pendantbooks.com/2013/03/26/just-do-the-work.html</link>
		<description><![CDATA[Just do the work! There is no other way to say it. Forget all the opposition. Forget all the millions of reasons not to. Forget your exhaustion, your discouragement]]></description>
		
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>You Are No Shakespeare</title>
		<pubDate>Wed, 5 Dec 2012 14:33:00 MDT</pubDate>
		<link>http://www.pendantbooks.com/2012/12/05/you-are-no-shakespeare.html</link>
		<description><![CDATA[“You are no Shakespeare!” That is what the little voice inside my head used to constantly remind me as I reviewed my own work (still does on occasion). It never failed]]></description>
		
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The Gate</title>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2012 14:33:00 MDT</pubDate>
		<link>http://www.pendantbooks.com/2012/11/20/the-gate.html</link>
		<description><![CDATA[All my life I wanted to write novels. I can still remember my earliest experiences of sitting down with my brother, Jared, when I was about eight and excitedly dashing off page]]></description>
		
	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
